visa.com.hk 2001-12-16

# Visa-Privacy Matters

|    

Legal

Downloads

|  |  

Privacy Matters

* * *

Revised April 2001 

Depending on what you do when you visit any web site, you are providing information about your visit to the site's owners. This includes Visa-Asia.com. We value privacy and think you do too, so we want you to have the information you need to make your own decisions about your personal privacy. When you visit or supply information to any web site, we think it's a good idea for you to first understand what that site's privacy policies are. If the site doesn't tell you, don't hesitate to ask. 

  The bottom line at [www.visa-asia.com](http://www.visa-asia.com/) is that we use the information that we get from your visit for internal tracking purposes, to make Visa-Asia.com as useful and interesting to you as we can, and to respond to your requests for information or other services. Except as specifically noted, we do not use your personal information for any other purpose; we never sell it to any third party; and, we never share it with any third party. 

  Read more about:

| I.  | Notice  
---|---  
| | \- What personal information we collect and how we use your information  
|     | \- Our policy regarding sharing of information  
II.| Choice  
|     | \- How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us  
III.| Access  
|     | \- How you can control the use of your personal information  
IV.| Security  
|     | \- How we protect the security of your personal information  
V. | Customer Service and Recourse  
|     | \- Changes to the Visa-Asia.com Privacy Policy  
|     | \- How to contact Visa-Asia.com  
  
  **I. Notice**

 What personal information we collect and how we use your information: When you visit the Visa-Asia.com web site, we capture the internet provider's domain name and country that you came from (e.g., 'aol.com') and the paths taken as you move from page to page (i.e., your "click stream" activity). 

 Information we collect on Visa-Asia.com may be used to enhance your use of this web site in ways like these: \- Arrange the web site in the most user-friendly way \- Customize your browsing experience of this web site \- Communicate special offers and featured items to you, if you choose to receive such notices \- Respond to your question or suggestions 

  **Visitor Registration or Requests for Information:**

  Visa-Asia.com only collects personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using or registering with the Visa-Asia.com site. "Personal information" includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address; and, in the case of license agreements, your name and company name. While you can browse our site without registering, you will need to register in order to take advantage of certain features, such as requesting updates on promotional offers. 

  Visa-Asia.com will on occasion ask you to voluntarily submit information about other people. For example, you might be asked to submit a person's email address to inform them about a sweepstakes or contest offered on Visa-Asia.com. The type of personally identifiable information that may be requested about other people may include the person's name and email address. Visa-Asia.com may use this information to inform them about a sweepstakes or contest. 

  **Browsing and the use of Cookies:**

  Visa-Asia.com uses cookie technology as part of our web site's statistical reporting. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience (i.e., rotating images on Visa-Asia.com home page) and to gather web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the internet provider's domain name and country that our visitors come from (e.g. 'aol.com,' or 'umich.edu') and the addresses of sites visited immediately before, and after, coming to Visa-Asia.com. However, none of this is associated with you as an individual. It is measured only in aggregate. The information in the cookies lets us trace your "click stream" activity (i.e., the paths taken by visitors to our site as they move from page to page. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you. 

  We also use standard web server log files to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical capacity. We use this information to find out how many people visit Visa-Asia.com, help us arrange the pages in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, and to make our pages more useful to our visitors. We record information on site traffic but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used. 

  To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies, or to notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) 

  **Sweepstakes, Trivia Games, and Surveys:**

  From time to time, Visa-Asia.com may conduct sweepstakes, trivia games, or surveys via our web site. If you choose to participate, we use your response to select sweepstakes winners, to come up with the game or survey results and, sometimes, to publish those results in aggregate on the site. Except where necessary to run a sweepstakes, we will never permanently record or report any response you give on its own or connect it to your name or address. We will hold these responses only as anonymous statistics. We will never sell or rent such information to any third parties. 

  **Email, Mailing Lists, and Other Services:**

  When you send us an email, we use your email address to thank you for your comment and/or reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use. 

  When you request information or other services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided with each email and/or on the site where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use. 

  **Linking To Other Sites:**

  Please remember that when you use a link to go from Visa-Asia.com to another web site, the Visa-Asia.com Site Rules and this Privacy Policy are no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other web site, including any site that has a link on Visa-Asia.com, is subject to the rules and policies of that site. We encourage you to read the rules and policies of the sites you visit to further understand their procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing personal information. 

  Top of Page

  **Our policy regarding sharing of information:**

 Our policy is simple: we never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. 

  Top of Page

  **II. Choice**

  **How you can decide what communication you'll receive from us:**

  If you choose to receive them, Visa-Asia.com may periodically send you email messages describing updates, new features, or promotional offers related to this web site. You can choose to stop receiving this email at any time. Simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request. 

  If you do not explicitly choose to receive informational emails, the only email messages you will receive from Visa-Asia.com will be to respond to email inquiries that you send us. 

  Top of Page

  **III.Access**

  **How to update or correct your personal information:**

  To modify or delete your personal information, simply follow the instructions included in your email, or send a reply stating your request, and we will make the requested changes. 

  Top of Page

  **IV. Security**

  **How we protect the security of your personal information:**

  The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. Visa-Asia.com uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our web site. 

  Top of Page

  **V. Customer Service and Recourse**

  **Changes to the Visa-Asia.com Privacy Policy**

  This Privacy Policy was posted in April 2001. Visa-Asia.com reserves the right to change, modify or amend this policy at any time. Please also read over the Visa-Asia.com Site Rules. Visa takes privacy matters very seriously, and intends to stay at the forefront of privacy policy and protection matters. Visa will occasionally update our privacy policy and we will post those updates on this page. You are responsible for revisiting this page to review our privacy policy updates. 

  Top of Page

  **How to contact Visa-Asia.com:**

  Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any Visa-Asia.com related services, you consent to Visa's processing of this information in the United States as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. 

  If you have any questions, comments, criticisms, or complaints about Visa-Asia.com's privacy policy and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to [email us](mailto:askvisa@visa.com). 

  Top of Page

Home | Products & Services | Offers & Promotions | Consumer Tips  
For Businesses | Sponsorships & Events | New Technologies | About Visa

Legal | Privacy | Downloads

© Copyright, 2001, Visa International. All rights reserved.
